[Music]
blessings everyone this is Chris Kendall
from the rod vantage.com register
holistic nutritionist raford lifestyle
coach and raw Chef today we're going to
make some raw peanut pad tie let's get
into it baby I like ra yeah baby I Like
It
Raw all right so this is a really fun
raw fi rendition of kind of like classic
peanut pad tie you're going to want to
start by sourcing good quality raw
peanuts and then soaking them for 12
hours and then fully dehydrating them
this gives them a much better crispier
texture also it remove some of the
alphat toxin the noodles itself you can
really do anything you want but I'm
going to share what I'm enjoying what I
had ingredients for here and what is one
of my favorite classic ways to do it so
I'm starting with a base of cucumber
noodles and those noodles are just from
the outside so you might need two big
cucumbers or one big one we got some
Nappa cabbage one of my favorite ways to
do noodles just really thinly sliced we
got some baby boach Choy also really
thinly sliced like noodles some red
cabbage thinly sliced which you could
freeze and Tha beforehand to have it an
even softer noodle really thinly sliced
red peppers we got a whole bunch of
pitted dates this is what we're getting
into for the sauce one garlic a little
bit of onion that's the base of the bok
choy got some ginger cut up green onion
for garnish now this is pretty unique
this is amure mango powder
you could also use Tamarind if you want
and then a half a cup of those soaked
and dehydrated peanuts we're going to
start by put all the peanuts in the
Vitamix blender you can get your blender
in the description below with free
shipping we're just going to give them a
pulse we don't want them completely
Blended
up look at that pour about half of that
back into measuring cup there we go
leave the rest in the blender container
add all the
dates the ginger I like a lot of Ginger
you can use half this amount if you like
or less the garlic you can feel free to
Omit or use garlic powder for a milder
flavor the onion and the bok choy bottom
which is just because I don't want to
throw it away a tie chili the mango
powder or equivalent amount of Tamarind
pulp and meow meow meow almost one cup
of water ideal if it's quite warm I'll
make a nice warmer sauce I like to start
with about 3/4 of it blend and then add
just to make a thick thick paste blend
until it's
smooth you want it really thick because
the noodles are watery and when you add
them together it'll pull some of the
water from there so if you don't want it
to be runny nice and thick is the key
all right so we got all the ingredients
in here you can just mix it all up you
know might be easier if you don't just
use your hands but put this sauce right
on top get in there you get in there
it's really meant to be thick like this
I promise you trust me unless you're
going to eat it like immediately it's
better if it's really thick like this
that mango powder or otherwise Tamarind
gives the classic sourness while of
course the date gives the classic
sweetness of the pad tie and all the
flavors melt together to make this an
authentic tasting fresh crunchy vibrant
waterr dish we'll just stir that
up oh yeah look at how look look at
would you just look at that starting to
look authentic
is
and let me go the peanuts on top you
could mix that in and then add more on
top if you want let's let's go for it
let's just get a little bit in there so
that you don't have to keep on doing
it there we go look at that and the
final Spritz of
peanuts oh and we can't forget a garnish
of fresh chives or green onions look at
that look at that you look at
it and there you have it raw peanut pad
thae let's test it
[Music]
out it's damn good you're going to want
to try it trust
me for tons of more recipes like this
check out my freaking rwome playlist get
my free app sign up for more subscribe
like comment do all those good things
come on you know it's time stra down
there it's easy as always wishing you
much peace love and seasonal
fruit raw vegan peanut pad
tie go on give it a try grab your free
raw recipe app available on iPhone and
Android with over 100 free raw recipes
common fruit and vegetable calorie
breakdown freaking rossom food combining
chart shopping cart function and so much
more